rmauctions.com 2017-09-21

# Privacy Policy | Classic Car Auctions | RM Sotheby's

**RM Auctions Inc. Personal Data Privacy and Protection Policy**   
RM Auctions Inc. considers the privacy and protection of its clients' personal data to be of utmost importance. To ensure that you feel confident about providing us with your personal information when communicating with us and using our services, we outline below our practices in relation to the collection and use of personal data. 

**_Purposes_**   
RM Auctions Inc. will collect, record, store, and use your personal data worldwide, but only to enable you to consign or purchase items or services and, unless you object, to advise you of forthcoming sales, events, and services. 

**_Privacy_**   
We will not share your personal data with anyone outside the RM Auctions Inc. group of companies. 

We may from time to time, however, need to disclose your personal data to agents or contractors of RM Auctions Inc. to enable RM Auctions Inc. to process transactions or communicate with you. When we do so, it will be on the basis that they are required to keep the information confidential, and they will not use the information for any other purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for RM Auctions Inc. 

**_Security_**   
Any personal data you provide to us is securely stored in a database held by RM Auctions Inc. in Ontario and/or RM Auctions Inc. in the United Kingdom, to which only authorized RM Auctions Inc. employees and agents have access. 

We have put in place administrative measures to ensure that the access that RM Auctions Inc. employees and agents have to personal data on our server is limited to the extent necessary in order to perform their functions. 

The server holding your personal data is protected against both unauthorized physical and electronic access. These measures include an electronic firewall and various other protection measures that involve virus scanning, the installation of security patches, vulnerability testing, backup and recovery planning, employee training, security audits, and other steps designed to constantly improve the data protection posture. The server is not directly connected to the Internet, so, therefore, the data is available only to authorized computers. 

**RM Auctions Inc. and the Internet**

**_Website_**   
In general, you may browse our Internet site anonymously. However, certain of our online services require the collection of some personally identifying information, such as your name, address, and, when appropriate, your credit information. 

For transactions over the RM Auctions Inc. website that involve particularly sensitive information, such as credit card numbers and accounting information, RM Auctions Inc. will employ accepted transmission and storage protocols, such as encryption, to prevent this information from being disclosed. This means that when you type in sensitive information, such as credit card details, it will be automatically converted into codes before being securely sent to us over the Internet. 

This information will be used for processing transactions, but it may also be used for internal data processing, such as compiling statistical information about your interests and the use of our Internet site. As a service to you, we may also use this information to customize the content we offer. 

**_Email_**   
In order to provide you with timely notice about upcoming auctions and events, RM Auctions Inc. may send you e-mail notices based on your expressed interests and bidding history. To facilitate this service, RM Auctions Inc. may note some of the pages you visit on our website. 

At the bottom of each e-mail you will be provided with the option to update your collecting interests or unsubscribe from future mailings. At any time, you may also send an e-mail requesting that your e-mail address be removed from our lists. 

**_Business Relationships_**   
The RM Auctions Inc. sites contain links to other websites. None of the information that you provide to us will be transmitted to other websites. RM Auctions Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

**_Cookies_**   
RM Auctions Inc. may also use on its Internet properties a personalization technology called a "cookie." A cookie is a small text file placed on your computer's hard disk that identifies your browser software to a website. Cookies allow us to track when you enter, leave, and re-enter our sites, and what path you take through our sites. In doing this, we can provide you with a more personalized experience. 

**_Alert a Friend_**   
RM Auctions Inc. provides users of this site the opportunity to inform others (each a "recipient") about a sale or lot for sale, which will require the sender to provide the recipient's e-mail address(es). At the sender's request, RM Auctions Inc. will automatically send the recipient an e-mail on behalf of the sender with a link to RM Auctions Inc.â€™s site, which will contain the information about the sale or lot. RM Auctions Inc. will not initiate any further contact with the recipient, beyond the e-mail sent on behalf of the sender, unless the recipient specifically "subscribes" for extra services by filling out a registration form. 

If you, as a recipient, do not wish to receive further e-mails from the sender, please reply to the sender requesting that they stop sending you e-mails in the future. RM Auctions Inc. does not accept responsibility for any third party's use (or misuse) of this service. 

**_Security_**   
RM Auctions Inc. will take reasonable steps to protect the security and integrity of all personal information provided to this website, including making your sensitive information available to our employees and agents on a need-to-know basis. However, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. 

If you contact us by e-mail or a "Contact Us" or similar feature on our website, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit. 

You may be able to create an account on our website with a username and password. Passwords are encrypted, and RM Auctions Inc. policies preclude access to passwords by anyone at RM Auctions Inc. or its service providers, except on a need-to-know basis. If you do create a username and password, you are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account password, and you shall be responsible for any access to or use of the website by you or any person or entity using your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by or on behalf of you and whether or not such person or entity is your employee or agent. You agree to (a) immediately notify RM Auctions Inc. of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security and (b) ensure that you exit from you're account at the end of each session. It is your sole responsibility to control the dissemination and use of your password, control access to and use of your account, and notify RM Auctions Inc. when you desire to cancel your account on this website. We will not be responsible or liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this provision. We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission. 

In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personal information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent that we have your e-mail address, we may notify you be e-mail. You consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification. If you prefer for us to use another method to notify you in this situation, please e-mail us with the alternative contact information you wish to be used. 

**_Phishing_**   
With identity theft a continuing problem, it has become increasingly common for unauthorized individuals to send e-mail messages to the consumer, purporting to represent a legitimate company such as a bank or online merchant, requesting that the consumer provide personal, often sensitive information. Sometimes, the domain name of the e-mail address from which the e-mail appears to have been sent, and the domain name of the website requesting such information, appears to be the domain name of a legitimate, trusted company. In reality, such sensitive information is received by an unauthorized individual to be used for purposes of identity theft. This illegal activity has come to be known as "phishing." 

If you receive an e-mail or other correspondence requesting that you provide any sensitive information (including your website password or credit card information) via e-mail or to a website that does not seem to be affiliated with our website, or to one that otherwise seems suspicious to you, please do not provide such information and report such requests to the Legal Department at +1 519 352 4575. 

**_Consent to Worldwide Transfer and Processing of Personal Data_**   

RM Auctions Inc. is a global enterprise, with affiliates in North America and Europe. When you give your personally identifiable information to RM Auctions Inc., it will be processed by RM Auctions Inc. in all countries in which we have affiliates. Each of these countries has different privacy laws that afford varying levels of protection for your personally identifiable information. Regardless of the laws in place in these countries, RM Auctions Inc. will treat the privacy of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By providing your personally identifiable information to RM Auctions Inc., you consent to RM Auctions Inc. and to the processing of your information in, any jurisdiction, in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Exceptions**   
While we will not voluntarily disclose your personal data, we may disclose such information if we are required to do so by a Court Order, if we are requested by government or law enforcement authorities, if we are required to do so in pursuant to other legal processes, or if it becomes necessary to protect the rights or property of RM Auctions Inc. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**   
RM Auctions Inc. reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of this website by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this website. Under certain circumstances, we also may notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our website or by sending you an e-mail. 

**Contact**   
RM Auctions Inc. reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of this website by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this website. Under certain circumstances, we also may notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our website or by sending you an e-mail.
